(Sheldon(exiting while the door is open):)Finally.
(Sheldon(exiting while the door is open):)Oh, what fresh hell is this?
(Doctor:)Wait, you can't leave here,
you've been exposed.
(Sheldon:)No, I haven't.
(Sheldon:)It's all good.
(Penny:)You want to talk
about crazy mothers,
(Penny:)Leonard's mom wouldn't give him
any sort of approval growing up.
(Priya:)Oh, the poor thing.
(Penny:)It makes him desperate
to please women.
(Penny:)That's why the foreplay
goes on and on.
(Priya:)It does, doesn't it?
(Penny:)It's like he's
trying to win a prize.
(Penny:)A word of advice--
don't doze off.
(Penny:)You will never hear
the end of it.
(Sheldon(through glass door pane):)Help me!
(Sheldon(through glass door pane):)Come back!
(Sheldon(through glass door pane):)Penny!